

Profile

- Top skills: JavaScript, React, NextJS, Vue
- Creative Front-End Developer offering 9+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations.
 Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Front-End Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

HMW Consulting

United States

September 2020 - September 2021(1 year 1 month) / Remote

- \cdot Developed membership, event, and legal platform technology solutions, and automated internal processes.
- \cdot Generated \$50K+ in annual ad revenue as a system administrator of a large network of websites.
- · Designed and implemented web applications along with 3rd-party software integrations as a web team liaison for all interdepartmental and customer-facing projects.
- · Developed a node.js server to validate membership and track digital badges being used, saving the company \$22.5K.
- \cdot Mentored 6 team members, enabling them to achieve professional growth and personal goals.

React Developer

Skip The Dishes Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada

March 2019 - April 2020 Fulltime | Remote

- · Participated in the initial wave of developers learning and implementing the React.JS library.
- ·Rewrote HTML to meet industry and company standards for SEO and Accessibility.
- •Developed the web page used for training healthcare professionals. Implemented a Web app used to follow up the routine of persons with breast cancer treatment.

Software Engineer

Effy Jewelry New York, United States

March 2019 - April 2020 Remote

Processed and fulfilled customer orders via the phone and Shopify

CONTACT

Mexico City Metropolitan Area (210) 920-7382

micael.dev216@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/mi chael-wen628

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science University of Toronto 2007-2011

SKILLS

Languages

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

C++

PHP

Libraries

React / TypeScript

JQUERY

Redux

Frameworks

Angular.js(versions 2-9)

Node.js

Express

Vue

CI/CD

GIT

Other Skills

AWS Services

GRAPHQL API

WebSocket

WebRTC

MySQL

MongoDB